Register of the Josef Škvorecký Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1919-1994. (Box 13-72)
  - Navrátilová, Martina, 1976-1990 (Box-folder 53: 1)
  - Nedoma, Zora, 1984 (Folder 53: 2)
  - Nedomanský, Václav, 1979 (Folder 53: 3)
  - Neduha, 1984 (Folder 53: 4)
  - Nejezchleba, Přemysl, 1977-1984 (Folder 53: 5)
  - Němcová, Jeanne, 1968-1992 (Folder 53: 6)
  - Němec, Jan, 1977-1986 (Folder 53: 7)
  - Němec, Jiří, 1987 (Folder 53: 8)
  - Nesvadba, Josef, 1971-1994 (Folder 53: 9)
  - Netopil, Rostislav, 1980-1981 (Folder 53: 10)
  - Neudorflová, Marie, 1984 (Folder 53: 11)
  - Neuhard, Elsa, 1971-1973 (Folder 53: 12)
  - Neuhart, Marie, n.d. (Folder 53: 13)
  - Novák, Adam, 1980 (Folder 53: 14)
  - Novák, Jan, 1977-1994 (Folder 53: 15-17)
  - Novák, Josef, 1970-1986 (Box-folder 54: 1)
  - Nováková, Eva, 1988 (Folder 54: 2)
  - Novotná, 1986-1989 (Folder 54: 3)
  - Novotná, Zdena, 1971-1994 (Folder 54: 4)
  - Novotný, Tomáš, 1986-1988 (Folder 54: 5)
  - Novotných, 1980-1986 (Folder 54: 6)
  - Ochová, Sheila, 1971-1972 (Folder 54: 7)
  - Odeon nakladatelství, 1971-1972 (Folder 54: 8)
  - Otčenášek, Karel, 1992-1993 (Folder 54: 9)
  - Otruba, Zdeněk, 1971, 1989 (Folder 54: 10)
  - Otta, 1992 (Folder 54: 11)
  - Pachman, Luděk, 1973-1981 (Folder 54: 12)
  - Palach Press, 1985-1986 (Folder 54: 13)
  - Pallas, Jiří, 1977-1987 (Folder 54: 14)
  - Panenová, Květa, 1980-1984 (Folder 54: 15)
  - Páral, Vladimír, 1989-1993 (Folder 54: 16)
  - Parrott, Cecil, 1977 (Folder 54: 17)
  - Pašek, Petr, 1978-1981 (Folder 54: 18)
  - Pašič, Nick, 1981 (Folder 54: 19)
  - Passer, 1986 (Folder 54: 20)
  - Patočka, Jan, n.d. (Folder 54: 21)
  - Pavel, Jiří, 1980 (Folder 54: 22)
  - Pecháček, 1987-1989 (Folder 54: 23)
  - Pecka, Karel, 1972-1992 (Folder 54: 24)
  - Pejskar, Josef, 1971-1973, 1992-1993 (Folder 54: 25)
  - Pekárková, Iva, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 55: 1)
  - Pelc, Jan, 1984-1990 (Folder 55: 2)
  - Pelikán, Jiří, 1979-1989 (Folder 55: 3)
  - Penzler, Otto, 1983 (Folder 55: 4)
  - Peroutka, Ferdinand, 1971-1991 (Folder 55: 5)
  - Petřík, V., 1985 (Folder 55: 6)
  - Petro, Peter, 1988 (Folder 55: 7)
  - Pfaff, Ivan, 1971-1990 (Folder 55: 8)
  - Pfeffer, 1981 (Folder 55: 9)
  - Picek, Jan, 1980-1986 (Folder 55: 10)
  - Píka, 1989-1990 (Folder 55: 11)
  - Pilarová, Eva, 1970, 1985-1994 (Folder 55: 12)
  - Pinkava, Václav, 1980-1986 (Folder 55: 13)
  - Pinkava, Václav, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 56: 1)
  - Pišta, Jan, 1992 (Folder 56: 2)
  - Pitaš, 1982-1984 (Folder 56: 3)
  - Planner, George J., 1992 (Folder 56: 4)
  - Plastic People, 1983 (Folder 56: 5)
  - Pletánek, Václav, 1980-1981 (Folder 56: 6)
  - Plumlovský, 1978-1980 (Folder 56: 7)
  - Podhoretz, Norman, 1986 (Folder 56: 8)
  - Pohribny, Arsén, 1984 (Folder 56: 9)
  - Poláčková, Káča, 1987-1993 (Folder 56: 10)
  - Polesý, H., 1984 (Folder 56: 11)
  - Ponická, Hana, 1987-1990 (Folder 56: 12)
  - Pořízka, Jiří, 1974-1975 (Folder 56: 13)
  - Poupová, Taťána, 1980 (Folder 56: 14)
  - Powers, Robert, 1987-1988 (Folder 56: 15)
  - Prečan, Vilém, 1979-1992 (Folder 56: 16-17)
  - Preisner, Rio, 1976-1984 (Folder 56: 18)
  - Přenosilová, 1982 (Folder 56: 19)
  - Přibík, Jindřich, 1979-1981 (Folder 56: 20)
  - Procházková, Eva, 1983-1984 (Folder 56: 21)
  - Procházková, Iva, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 57: 1)
  - Procházková, Lenka, 1981-1991 (Folder 57: 2)
  - Procházková, Marta, 1986-1988 (Folder 57: 3)
  - Prošek, 1988 (Folder 57: 4)
  - Provazníková, Marie, 1976-1977 (Folder 57: 5)
  - Putík, Jaroslav, 1989 (Folder 57: 6)
  - Rada, Petr, 1978-1987 (Folder 57: 7)
  - Radok, Alfred, 1971 (Folder 57: 8)
  - Radová, Lucie, 1981-1982 (Folder 57: 9)
  - Rambousek, Ota, 1971-1991 (Folder 57: 10)
  - Rechcígl, Miloslav, 1988 (Folder 57: 11)
  - Rechner, Vincent, 1986-1994 (Folder 57: 12)
  - Reich Verlag, 1976-1985 (Folder 57: 13)
  - Reichovi, 1981-1983 (Folder 57: 14)
  - Reiniš, Stanislav, 1990-1993 (Folder 57: 15)
  - Rektořík, 1980-1981 (Folder 58: 1)
  - Renský, Miroslav, 1981 (Folder 58: 2)
  - Řesáč, Jan, 1980-1991 (Folder 58: 3)
  - Řezníček, Ivo, 1979-1994 (Folder 58: 4)
  - Rheinwald, Eva, 1981-1982 (Folder 58: 5)
  - Ribnikar, Jara, 1989-1994 (Folder 58: 6)
  - Rich, Jana, 1994 (Folder 58: 7)
  - Richterová, Sylvie, 1979-1993 (Folder 58: 8)
  - Rollerová, Věra, 1992 (Folder 58: 9)
  - Roth, Philip, 1982-1995 (Folder 58: 10)
  - Roth, Susanna, 1980-1990 (Folder 58: 11)
  - Rotrekl, Zdeněk, 1986-1989 (Folder 58: 12)
  - Rudajev, Alexandre, 1984 (Folder 58: 13)
  - Ruljancic, Dagmar, 1984-1986 (Folder 58: 14)
  - Rybáková, Minka, 1990 (Folder 58: 15)
  - Ryšavá, Michele, 1981 (Folder 58: 16)
  - Sabatová, Anna, 1991 (Box-folder 59: 1)
  - Sacher, Vilém, 1978 (Folder 59: 2)
  - Safařík, Bernard, 1984 (Folder 59: 3)
  - Salaquarda, Karel, 1971/1973, 1983/1994 (Folder 59: 4)
  - Savage, Stephanie, 1994 (Folder 59: 5)
  - Savrda, Jiří, 1983 (Folder 59: 6)
  - Schejbal, Jaroslav, 1982 (Folder 59: 7)
  - Scheuerová, Lísa, 1983 (Folder 59: 8)
  - Schilling, J., 1976 (Folder 59: 9)
  - Schirger, Alexander, 1981 (Folder 59: 10)
  - Schonberg, Pasia, 1985-1994 (Folder 59: 11-12)
  - Schorm, Ewald, n.d. (Folder 59: 13)
  - Schulz, Milan, n.d. (Folder 59: 14)
  - Segert, Stanislav, 1981 (Folder 59: 15)
  - Seifert, Jaroslav, 1977-1987 (Box-folder 60: 1-3)
  - Sekanina, Clemens, 1988 (Folder 60: 4)
  - Semerádovi, 1987 (Folder 60: 5)
  - Serke, Juergen, 1981 (Folder 60: 6)
  - Sidon, Karol, 1978-1980 (Folder 60: 7)
  - Sikl, Václav, 1973-1989 (Folder 60: 8)
  - Siklová, 1982 (Folder 60: 9)
  - Silhánek, Vladimír, 1983-1991 (Folder 60: 10)
  - Sillitoe, 1980-1984 (Folder 60: 11)
  - Similichová, Marie, 1980 (Folder 60: 12)
  - Simko, Dušan, 1978-1985 (Folder 60: 13)
  - Simková, Dáša, 1978-1990 (Folder 60: 14)
  - Síp, Michal, 1977-1983 (Folder 60: 15)
  - Sjoeblom, Alice "Babs," 1982-1992 (Box-folder 61: 1)
  - Skácel, Jan, 1977-1980 (Folder 61: 2)
  - Skalka, Miloš, 1970-1984 (Folder 61: 3)
  - Skilling, H. Gordon, 1971, 1984-1988 (Folder 61: 4)
  - Skov, Zuzana, 1970-1985 (Folder 61: 5)
  - Skrabánková, Lenka, 1986-1988 (Folder 61: 6)
  - Skutina, Vladimír, 1975-1988 (Folder 61: 7-8)
  - Skvor, Jiří, 1970-1983 (Folder 61: 9)
  - Smetana, František, 1983 (Folder 62: 1)
  - Smithin, Hana, 1980-1984 (Folder 62: 2)
  - Snepp, Luděk, 1971-1988 (Folder 62: 3)
  - Solar, William, 1980-1981 (Folder 62: 4)
  - Solecki, Sam, 1984-1993 (Folder 62: 5)
  - Sontag, Susan, 1980-1987 (Folder 62: 6)
  - Souček, David, 1968-1986 (Folder 62: 7)
  - Souček, Jan, 1971-1993 (Folder 62: 8)
  - Součková, Milada, 1978-1982 (Folder 62: 9)
  - Soukup, Alena, 1989 (Folder 62: 10)
  - Spacek, Edwin and Sissy, 1984 (Folder 62: 11)
  - Spaniel, Bohumír, 1970-1993 (Folder 62: 12)
  - Spirit, Michael, 1989-1994 (Folder 62: 13)
  - Srba, A. J., 1971 (Folder 62: 14)
  - Srych, Josef, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 63: 1)
  - Stafl, Jaja, 1981-1985 (Folder 63: 2)
  - Stankiewicz, Markéta Goetz, 1973-1993 (Folder 63: 3)
  - Staňková, Maruška, 1992-1993 (Folder 63: 4)
  - Stankovič, Andrej, 1970 (Folder 63: 5)
  - Stavinoha, Jan, 1985-1987 (Folder 63: 6)
  - Steiger, Ivan, 1971-1984 (Folder 63: 7)
  - Steinbach, Karel, 1982-1988 (Folder 63: 8)
  - Steiner, Frank, 1985 (Folder 63: 9)
  - Steiner, George, 1979 (Folder 63: 10)
  - Steiner, Peter, 1985 (Folder 63: 11)
  - Stejskal, Josef, 1983-1984 (Folder 63: 12)
  - Stichová, Marie, 1980-1990 (Folder 63: 13)
  - Stoppard, Tom, 1977-1984 (Folder 63: 14)
  - Stránský, Jiří, 1991 (Folder 63: 15)
  - Strick, Joseph, 1969-1990 (Folder 63: 16)
  - Strnad, Jaroslav, 1973-1989 (Folder 63: 17)
  - Strož, Daniel, 1978-1991 (Box-folder 64: 1)
  - Stuchliková, Jarka, 1969-1990 (Folder 64: 2)
  - Styron, William, 1965-1988 (Folder 64: 3)
  - Suchma, Miloš, 1971-1993 (Folder 64: 4-5)
  - Suchý, Ondřej and Jiří, 1990-1992 (Folder 64: 6)
  - Sus, Oleg, 1970-1971 (Folder 64: 7)
  - Sváb, Ludvík, 1987-1992 (Folder 64: 8)
  - Svejda, Michal Jan, 1984 (Folder 64: 9)
  - Svejk Society, 1982-1986 (Folder 64: 10)
  - Svestka, Jaroslav, 1982-1991 (Folder 64: 11)
  - Sviták, Ivan, 1936-1991 (Box-folder 65: 1-2)
  - Svobodná Evropa (Radio Free Europe), 1977-1986 (Folder 65: 3)
  - Svobodová, Eva, 1983 (Folder 65: 4)
  - SVU (Společnost pro vědy a umění), 1971, 1984 (Folder 65: 5)
  - Swinkels-Nováková, Michaela, 1970-1993 (Folder 65: 6-7)
  - Sýkora, Jiří, 1978-1983 (Folder 65: 8)
  - Syrovátko, Josef, 1980-1990 (Folder 65: 9)
  - Táborský, Václav, 1980-1988 (Folder 65: 10)
  - Tatarka, Dominik, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 66: 1)
  - Taussig, Pavel, 1981-1990 (Folder 66: 2)
  - Taussigová-Potůčková, Jarmila, 1979 (Folder 66: 3)
  - Taylor, Líba, 1977-1990 (Folder 66: 4)
  - Tesař, Petr, n.d. (Folder 66: 5)
  - Teuner, František, 1971-1981 (Folder 66: 6)
  - Teyrovský, Vladimír, 1978 (Folder 66: 7)
  - Theiner, Jiří, 1973-1988 (Folder 66: 8)
  - Thiele, Vladimír, 1987 (Folder 66: 9)
  - Thistlethwaite, Anthony, 1993 (Folder 66: 10)
  - Tigrid, Pavel, 1971-1994 (Folder 66: 11)
  - Tomin, Lukáš, 1980 (Folder 66: 12)
  - Tomský, Alexander, 1982-1988 (Folder 66: 13)
  - Topol, Jáchym, 1988-1993 (Folder 66: 14)
  - Tóth, Dušan, 1980 (Folder 66: 15)
  - Toufar, Josef, 1971-1972 (Folder 66: 16)
  - Townsend, Charles E., 1989 (Folder 66: 17)
  - Traxler, Jiří, 1919, 1976-1994 (Box-folder 67: 1)
  - Trdlicová, Květa, 1987-1988 (Folder 67: 2)
  - Trefulka, Jan, 1973-1988 (Folder 67: 3)
  - Trenský, 1993 (Folder 67: 4)
  - Třešňák, Vlasta, 1978-1988 (Folder 67: 5)
  - Trinkewitz, Karel, 1978-1986 (Folder 67: 6)
  - Tříska, Jan, 1983 (Folder 67: 7)
  - Troxel, Holly, 1986 (Folder 67: 8)
  - Turek, Jan, 1979 (Folder 67: 9)
  - Uhde, Milan and Dora, 1979-1993 (Folder 67: 10)
  - Ulč, Ota, 1970-1980 (Folder 67: 11)
  - Ulč, Ota, 1981-1994 (Box-folder 68: 1-4)
  - Updike, John, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 69: 1)
  - Urbánek, Zdeněk, 1984-1993 (Folder 69: 2)
  - Vachatová, Larissa, 1980-1982 (Folder 69: 3)
  - Vaculík, Ludvík, 1975-1994 (Folder 69: 4-5)
  - Váhala, Rastislav, 1978-1987 (Folder 69: 6)
  - Valenta, Vladimír, 1971, 1981-1993 (Folder 69: 7)
  - Vaněček, František, 1984-1986 (Folder 69: 8)
  - Vasa, Zuzana, 1985-1990 (Folder 69: 9)
  - Veis, Jaroslav, 1988 (Folder 69: 10)
  - Veit, Vladimír, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 70: 1)
  - Vejdělek, Čestmír, 1982-1987 (Folder 70: 2)
  - Vejvoda, Jaroslav, 1971-1984 (Folder 70: 3-4)
  - Velan, Karel, 1977-1991 (Folder 70: 5)
  - Vichtora, Franta, 1986 (Folder 70: 6)
  - Viklický, Emil, 1978-1991 (Folder 70: 7)
  - Vladislav, Jan, 1978-1994 (Folder 70: 8)
  - Vlček, Václav, 1990 (Folder 70: 9)
  - Vodičková, Marie, 1991 (Folder 70: 10)
  - Vodňanský, Jan, 1978-1991 (Folder 70: 11)
  - Vohryzek, Josef, 1992-1993 (Folder 70: 12)
  - Voice of America, 1972-1990 (Folder 70: 13)
  - Volný, Libor, 1993 (Folder 71: 1)
  - Vondráčková, Slávka, 1979 (Folder 71: 2)
  - Vonnegut, Kurt, 1988 (Folder 71: 3)
  - Vorel, Ladislav, 1983 (Folder 71: 4)
  - Voskovec, Jiří, 1957-1990 (Folder 71: 5-6)
  - Vostrá, Denisa, 1992 (Folder 71: 7)
  - Vrázová, Vlasta, 1981-1988 (Folder 71: 8)
  - Vyhňák, A., 1981-1984 (Folder 71: 9)
  - Vylupek, Josef, 1981 (Folder 71: 10)
  - Wagner, Arnošt, 1990-1993 (Folder 71: 11)
  - Weger, n.d. (Folder 71: 12)
  - Weilová, Olga, 1990-1991 (Folder 71: 13)
  - Wein, Jiří, 1988 (Folder 71: 14)
  - Weiss, Jiří, 1984-1988 (Folder 71: 15)
  - Wellek, Michael, 1991-1994 (Folder 71: 16)
  - Weller, Anthony, 1992 (Folder 71: 17)
  - Weller, Michael, 1985-1988 (Folder 71: 18)
  - Wilden, Theodore, 1971-1990 (Folder 71: 19)
  - Wilson, 1990-1991 (Folder 71: 20)
  - Winnová, Hanka, 1983 (Folder 71: 21)
  - Wolf, Peter H., 1978-1986 (Folder 71: 22)
  - Wonka, Jiří, 1990 (Folder 71: 23)
  - World Literature Today, 1980-1983 (Folder 71: 24)
  - Záběhlický, 1977 (Box-folder 72: 1)
  - Zábrana, Jan, 1931-1994 (Folder 72: 2-3)
  - Zábranová, 1977-1994 (Folder 72: 4)
  - Zahradníček, Jan, 1976-1979 (Folder 72: 5)
  - Zajíček, Tomaš, 1987 (Folder 72: 6)
  - Žák, Zdeněk, 1992-1994 (Folder 72: 7)
  - Žantovská, Hana, 1988-1994 (Folder 72: 8)
  - Zaoral, Zdeněk, 1980 (Folder 72: 9)
  - Zapletal, Zdeněk, 1989-1994 (Folder 72: 10)
  - Zástěra, Jaromír, 1981-1982 (Folder 72: 11)
  - Žekulin, 1993 (Folder 72: 12)
  - Zelená, Marie, 1980-1991 (Folder 72: 13)
  - Zelený, Milan, 1984 (Folder 72: 14)
  - Zemánková, Inka, 1988-1993 (Folder 72: 15)
    Includes 5 photographs glued to pages
  - Zvároví, 1971 (Folder 72: 16)
- Photographs, 1908-1994. (Box 73-79)
  Negatives, prints, slides, and transparencies, arranged by physical form, thereunder by series and folder from which the photographs were removed
  - Prints
    - Biographical File
      - Náchod a Hořice (Skvorecký's birthplace), n.d. (Folder 73: 1)
        2 unidentified black and white prints, 1 black and white print depicting Mařenka Skvorecká, 1 black and white print depicting the married couple Skvorecký, 1 black and white print depicting Zdena Pospíšilová, 1 black and white print depicting Anna Veselá, 1 black and white print depicting Dr. Erben, 1 black and white print depicting M. Reháčková, 1 black and white print depicting Miloslava Nýčová
      - Náchod a Hořice (Skvorecký's birthplace), 1935, 1949-1950, 1974, 1992. (Folder 73: 2)
        8 unidentified color prints, 8 unidentified black and white prints
    - Writings
      - Samožerbuch, 1980-1992. (Folder 73: 3)
        1 black and white print depicting Náchod, 54 unidentified black and white prints, 1 black and white print depicting Jan Řeháč, 1 black and white print depicting a demonstration on Václavském námestí in Prague, 1 black and white print depicting Prague, 1 black and white print depicting Pavlína Eichlerová, 63 unidentified color prints, 2 color prints depicting the Statue of Liberty, 4 color prints depicting family Zappner, 2 color prints depicting Jana Páclová, 1 color print depicting Stanislav Kadlec, 1 color print depicting family O'Connel, 8 color prints depicting Berlin, Germany, 2 color prints depicting Tamara and Richard Doležal, 1 color print depicting the painting Tiché snýdaně by Hedvika Krejčí, 4 color prints depicting Josef Skvorecký, 2 color prints depicting Ota Zvěřina
      - Scherzo capriccioso (Dvořák novel), 1980-1986. (Folder 73: 4)
        6 unidentified black and white prints, 2 black and white prints depicting Antonín Dvořák, 14 black and white prints depicting notes, one black and white print depicting Adele Margulies, 1 color print depicting Mike Beckerman, 12 unidentified color prints, 1 color print depicting the Dvořák Vineyard in Traben-Trarbach, Germany, 3 color prints depicting Anna Dvořáková, 1 color print depicting Anna Dvořáková-Čermáková, 1 color print depicting Antonín Dvořák
    - Correspondence
      - General. Authors of manuscripts (Autoři ruzných rukopisů), 1942, 1981, 1983. (Folder 73: 5)
        1 color print depicting Kamil Běhounek, 2 unidentified black and white prints
      - Auský, Stanislav, ca. 1940, 1977. (Folder 73: 6)
        1 unidentified black and white print, 1 unidentified color print, 1 color print depicting Stanislav Auský
      - Baarová, Lída, n.d. (Folder 73: 7)
        25 color prints depicting Lída Baarová, 2 unidentified color prints, 1 color print depicting Josef Skvorecký, 2 unidentified color prints
      - Barbier, Eva, 1986-1987. (Folder 73: 8)
        2 unidentified black and white prints, 4 color prints depicting Eva Barbier
      - Barborka, Emma P., 1980-1990. (Folder 73: 9)
        5 color prints depicting the Tomášek and Skálka families, 8 unidentified color prints, 3 unidentified black and white prints
      - Bartošek, Karel, 1984. (Folder 73: 10)
        1 color print depicting S. Roth and Bohumil Hrabal in Paris, 1 unidentified black and white print
      - Beer, Olinka Nesvadba, 1976. (Folder 73: 11)
        1 unidentified black and white print
      - Běhounek, Kamil, 1940, ca. 1955. (Folder 73: 12)
        9 unidentified black and white prints, 4 black and white prints depicting Evelyne Plessis, 1 black and white print depicting Eve Janot, 1 black and white print depicting El Tekke, Cyprus, 1 black and white print depicting the "Státní reální gymnasium" in Slaný, 1 black and white print depicting Kamil Běhounek's bedroom in Bonn, Germany, 1 black and white print depicting Kamil Běhounek's birth house in Blatná, 1 black and white print depicting the birth house of Kamil Běhounek's father, 1 black and white print depicting a street in Slaný, 17 black and white prints depicting Kamil Běhounek, 1 black and white print depicting Kamil Běhounek's mother, 1 black and white print depicting aunt Fanynka Běhounková, 1 black and white print depicting Ladislav Běhounek, 1 black and white print depicting Ata and Hermann Otten, 1 black and white print depicting Werner Raschek
      - Beneš, Jan, n.d. (Folder 73: 13)
        2 unidentified black and white prints
      - Blatný, Ivan, n.d. (Folder 73: 14)
        1 color print depicting Ivan Blatný's grave, 1 color print depicting Ivan Blatný's residence, 1 unidentified black and white print
      - Blažek, Vratislav and Hana, 1949-ca. 1975. (Folder 73: 15)
        4 unidentified color prints, 1 unidentified black and white print, 1 black and white print depicting Vratislav and Hana Blažek, 1 color print depicting Vratislav Blažek and Vladimír Skutina, 1 black and white print depicting Vratislav Blažek
      - Bondy, Egon, 1978-1980. (Folder 73: 16)
        6 black and white prints depicting Egon Bondy
      - Brázdová, Valerie, 1985. (Folder 73: 17)
      - Bristol, Barbara, n.d. (Folder 73: 18)
        3 black and white prints depicting Josef Skvorecký
      - Brousek, Antonín, n.d. (Folder 73: 19)
        2 black and white prints depicting Markéta Brousková
      - Brychta, Lída and Jan, n.d. (Folder 73: 20)
        1 unidentified black and white print, 1 black and white print depicting the painting Večerní stůl - olej, acrylic, asambláž
      - Čamrda, Zdeněk, 1981. (Folder 73: 21)
        2 unidentified color prints
      - Černý, Václav, n.d. (Box-folder 74: 1)
        5 unidentified black and white prints, 1 black and white print depicting Václav Černý, 1 color print depicting Václav Černý
      - Chadim, Václav, 1993. (Folder 74: 2)
        1 color print depicting Václav Chadim and family members
      - Charles, Veronika, 1986-1989. (Folder 74: 3)
        8 color prints depicting Matoush, Samuel and Alexandra Charles
      - Dědeček, Jiří, 1990. (Folder 74: 4)
        4 black and white prints depicting Jiří Dědeček, 1 color print depicting Jiří Dědeček
      - Disher, Hanyi, n.d. (Folder 74: 5)
        1 black and white print depicting František Moravec
      - Diviš, Ivan, n.d. (Folder 74: 6)
      - Dohnal, Dan, n.d.. (Folder 74: 7)
        2 color prints depicting Dan Dohnal
      - Dorůžka, Lubomír, 1986. (Folder 74: 8)
        22 color prints depicting Lubomír Dorůžka, 1 black and white print depicting Lubomír Dorůžka, 2 black and white prints depicting the picture 11. pražské jazzové dny
      - Drozd, Karel, 1985. (Folder 74: 9)
        2 color prints depicting Karel Drozd
      - Duffel, Peter, n.d. (Folder 74: 10)
        2 color prints depicting an article of Milan Kundera about Josef Skvorecky's book Feiglinge
      - Dyntarová, Marie, n.d. (Folder 74: 11)
        9 unidentified black and white prints
      - Effenberger, V., 1980. (Folder 74: 12)
        1 black and white print depicting a painting of Martin Stejskal
      - Eichlerová, Ladislava, 1987-1993. (Folder 74: 13)
        4 color prints depicting Ladislava Eichlerová and family members, 3 unidentified black and white prints
      - Elefteriadu, Tena, n.d. (Folder 74: 14)
      - Elznic, Lukáš, 1987. (Folder 74: 15)
        7 color prints depicting the Czechoslovak-German border
      - Emmer, Jarmila and Jan, 1986. (Folder 74: 16)
        1 color print and 1 black and white print depicting family Emmer, 1 unidentified color print
      - Fibírová, Járinka, n.d. (Folder 74: 17)
      - Filip, Ota, n.d. (Folder 74: 18)
        1 black and white print depicting Ota Filip, 3 unidentified black and white prints
      - Fleischer, Vladimír, 1972. (Folder 74: 19)
        1 black and white print depicting Vladimír Fleischer
      - Fodor, Jiří and Jindra, 1987-1988. (Folder 74: 20)
        3 color prints depicting the Fodor family
      - Forman, Miloš, n.d. (Folder 74: 21)
        7 black and white prints depicting Věra Křesadlová and family members, 1 color print depicting Václav Havel, 2 black and white prints depicting Věra Křesadlová, Jiří Suchý and Dáda Patrasová
      - Ginsberg, Allen, n.d. (Folder 74: 22)
        2 black and white prints depicting Allen Ginsberg
      - Greene, Graham, 1988. (Folder 74: 23)
        2 black and white prints depicting Graham Greene
      - Gruša, Jiří, n.d. (Folder 74: 24)
        2 black and white prints depicting Jiří Gruša
      - Hájek, Igor, n.d. (Folder 74: 25)
        1 black and white print depicting Igor Hájek, 1 black and white print depicting John Updike
      - Havel, Václav, ca. 1955-1990. (Folder 74: 26)
        3 black and white prints and 1 color print depicting Olga and Václav Havel and Zdena and Josef Skvorecký, 1 black and white print depicting Olga and Václav Havel and Alexander Dubček, 2 color and 14 black and white prints depicting Václav Havel, 20 black and white prints depicting scenes from Havel's theatre plays, 3 unidentified color and 4 unidentified black and white prints, 3 black and white prints depicting letters to Olga
      - Hejl, Vilém, 1979-1981. (Box-folder 75: 1)
        3 unidentified color prints
      - Hladký, Ivan, n.d. (Folder 75: 2)
        5 unidentified color prints
      - Hochman, Jiří, n.d. (Folder 75: 3)
      - Hodač, Jiří, n.d. (Folder 75: 4)
        1 black and white print depicting Karel Kalivoda, 1 black and white print depicting a policemen from Prague, 1 black and white print depicting a criminalistic laboratory in Prague, 1 black and white print depicting a dead boy, 1 black and white print depicting the prague jail na Pankráci, 1 black and white print depicting an avalanche rescue, 1 black and white print depicting an avalanche, 1 black and white print depicting a theft in a supermarket, 1 black and white print depicting two released prisoners
      - Hora, Karel, 1947-1971. (Folder 75: 5)
        6 black and white prints depicting Karel Hora
      - Horák, Antonín, 1980-1984. (Folder 75: 6)
        4 black and white prints depicting family Horák
      - Hornychová, Ladislava, 1950, 1979-1982. (Folder 75: 7)
        7 black and white prints depicting Ladislava Hornychová and her family, 1 color print depicting Hornychová's grandson Vašek, 2 unidentified black and white prints
      - Hostovský, Egon, 1908, ca. 1920, 1952-1957. (Folder 75: 8)
        11 black and white prints depicting Egon Hostovský and family members, 1 black and white print depicting Hostovský's birth house, 1 black and white print depicting Egon Hostovský, his wife and Inger Hagerup, 1 black and white print depicting Egon Hostovský, Jiří Pistorius and Jan Čep in Paris, 1 black and white print depicting Egon Hostovský, Janeček and Fremund in Paris, 1 unidentified black and white print
      - Hrabal, Bohumil, 1984-1987. (Folder 75: 9)
        4 black and white and 10 color prints depicting Bohumil Hrabal, 1 color print depicting Josef Skvorecký, 2 unidentified color prints, 1 unidentified black and white print
      - Hvížd'ala, Karel, 1979. (Folder 75: 10)
        2 black and white prints depicting Karel Hvížďala
      - Ingris Productions, n.d. (Folder 75: 11)
        1 unidentified color print
      - Jazzová sekce svazu hudebníků ČSR, n.d. (Folder 75: 12)
        2 color prints depicting a Finnish photography exhibition, 3 unidentified black and white prints, 1 unidentified color print
      - Jeřábek, Jaroslav, n.d. (Folder 75: 13)
      - Jirásek, Jan, 1983-1992. (Folder 75: 14)
        1 black and white print depicting students of the "Státní reálné gymnasium v Náchodě," 5 unidentified color prints